and the top our news here at 6:00 an
age-old dream becoming a reality a local
inventor has discovered a way here this
to use water to run your car it's a
major breakthrough that will no doubt
make motorists happy and as Ralph
Robinson explains the Pentagon is also
showing lots of interest in this project
water has always been considered a
precious commodity but Stan my's
invention may make it even more valuable
he has developed what's called a water
fuel cell it has taken the place of his
old gas tank the water fuel cell breaks
down water molecules into oxygen and
hydrogen the hydrogen is used to run his
Doom buggy I don't care if you use rain
water well water City Water ocean water
if you don't have any fresh water go
ahead and use snow if you don't have any
snow available to you they use salt
water because there's no adverse effect
to the fuel cell Myers started working
on this project four years ago he's not
a scientist he isn't even a chemist in
fact he never graduated from college
Myers was determined he says to design
something to protect this country from
oil embargos and we have calculated that
if we take the dune buggy from Los
Angeles to New York we would roughly use
22 gallons of water the Pentagon flew of
lieutenant colonel in last week to look
at Myers invention there's talk of
possibly using it in the Star Wars
defense program and to run army tanks
Myers is currently perfecting a water
fuel cell for cars it will cost about
$1,500 he says it won't need any
maintenance and you won't have to
replace it it'll be at least 2 years
before the fuel system goes into mass
production the data happens will be one
the fuel industry hates but it will'll
put a smile on the face of those who had
to say at one time or another fill her
up H off Robins as you can see many
patents have already been received and
many more are forthcoming to date over
42 patents have been applied for